The True Story of Cristiada
Outlaws - For Greater Glory is a history, drama,
action film directed by Dean Wright.
A chronicle of the Cristeros War (1926-1929), which was touched off by a rebellion
against the Mexican government's attempt to secularize the country.
Tulita, played by Eva Longoria.
Enrique Gorostieta Velarde, played by Andy Garcia.
Victoriano 'El Catorce' Ramirez, played by Oscar Isaac.
Father Christopher, played by Peter O'Toole.
Président Calles, played by Rubén Blades.
Adriana, played by Catalina Sandino Moreno.
For Greater Glory: The True Story of Cristiada, also known as Cristiada and as Outlaws, is a 2012 epic historical war
drama film directed by Dean Wright and written by Michael Love, based on the events of the Cristero War.
It stars Andy García, Eva Longoria, Oscar Isaac, Rubén Blades, Peter O'Toole (in his
last film appearance released in his lifetime), and Bruce Greenwood.
The film is the directorial debut for Wright, a veteran visual effects supervisor on films including The
Two Towers (2002) and The Return of the King (2003), and was released on June 1, 2012.
The tone is emotional.